Let's get started with another Wednesday Downtown. Welcome everyone.
Yes, thank you
Shall we begin?
Everyone please welcome our first presenter
Yasuko Mitsuura of Oasis
We're well acquainted
You're usually over there
Yes, this is my first time on this side
Good evening, thank you for having me
Honestly... it's just, really?
Do I have to dig into this?
It's bound to bring out the worst in women.
Really?
Really. It really is.
It's that damning, huh?
The theory I've brought is this-
If a profile picture has two girls
it belongs to the cute one
That's harsh...
It's heartless~
I think that might be possible
I think it is
Talents can be really bad
Yes, talents and models-
don't seem to be as bad about it
But just look at what women put in their blog posts.
They ask me for a picture to post saying "I worked with Mitsuura-san!"
So they take it-
Then they upload it.
When I go to check it, I'm shocked!
I look like some messy, deranged woman with my eyes half-shut!
What is with that?
It was like she was thinking "Well as long as I look good".
It's scary, truly.
How about you two?
I think a lot of my friends are similar.
They ask for a picture but-
They only look at themselves
Right?
I think it's best that if you ask for a photo,
you should let them take it for you
For sure
I think this is something only moderately cute girls do
Real cute girls have real cute friends
That fastball came out of nowhere-
right into my face
KERPOW, right?
I'm speechless
That's quite an opinion
It feels like you have a superiority complex
Coming up-
Does the profile picture belong to the cuter girl?
After that-
Can you bunt a home run?
Using an automatic pitching machine-
we put it to the test
Then, can you play telephone with various genres?
The theory that you are not considered a professional unless you have a perfect knowledge about your signature act
If a profile picture has two girls-
it belongs to the cute one, theory
I wonder if this will end up being true?
First, we searched for girls that have a profile picture with their friend in it
Then we asked nearby boys which is cuter
Finally we'll find out which one is the real owner
Will it be the cute one?
This was the first photo we found
A profile picture with friends, ages 25 and 22
Could you please tell us which of the girls in this photo is cuter?
The left
The one on the left is cutest
Left
The left one?
Yeah
With 3 votes to 0, the streets have chosen the girl on the left
So which one does the profile picture belong to?
Thank you for helping
They got her to come out
Sure enough
Ah, of course it is
It was the cute one
The picture makes her look cuter
Why did you use a pair photo here?
You shouldn't say that
To show off my looks
What exactly do you mean by that?
It's the image of herself she
wants to embody, right?
Initially I was just taking a selfie
But it didn't look very glamorous with me alone
"I'll take it with a friend"
"Then I'll upload it"
Those 2 things are-
what I consider
when I decide
By the way, which of you is more popular?
Well, she's younger so she gets more attention
Really?
That's embarrassing
I'm pathetic
She insists she didn't use her friend as a fashion accessory
Around how many guys have asked you out, total?
I haven't been counting, really
Do you have a rough estimate?
It doesn't have to be exact.
Probably around 40 or 50
Isn't that a lot?
Moving on
This pair photo
I think the one on the right is cuter
I also prefer the girl on the right
I also think the girl in center frame is cute
The judgment on the streets is "right"
Sure enough
They're correct after all
This one was also the cuter girl
With this there's a sense that
"Oh, they're such good friends!"
So, good friends
But a selfie kind of screams-
"I'm obsessed with myself"
Next
These two
I also think the left is cuter
I also say left
The decision is the girl on the left,
but could the picture belong-
to the plain girl in the middle?
It could be
Excuse me
Of course
It's the girl on the left
That's freaky~
Although the rate of cute girls using pictures is high,
most of the pair photos we found were equally cute
Do you think many women-
use pair photos with someone much less attractive?
It somehow exudes the sense that she is obviously cuter
Then, there's-
This pair photo
Could you please pick the cuter girl?
Oh for sure
The right one, yo
The one in white, right?
Yeah, that's right
The right
The one in white?
Yes.
The left one
Left?
Without the purikura effect,
I think the girl on the right is going to look worse
This is the first time the decision has split 2-1
So which one is the owner?
Ah, there she is. She's coming.
Hello
Excuse me, we're from Wednesday Downtown
And so-
We're not sure which girl this is
Which one?
In the purikura machine
This setting...
I think it's turned all the way up.
Somehow, the purikura created this totally distorted picture
At this point
It seems less about cuteness
And more about the effects used
Our next photo is this
I think the left is cuter
The left one
By some stroke of fate we ran into this man
Excuse me, excuse me
Haven't you been on TV before?
Have you been on TV?
Yes, I have
Wednesday Downtown
Yes
We're shooting Wednesday Downtown now
Oh really?
That's right, this man is-
Back from spring
the one we met when we were looking for fish-faces
The hippo-face man
What do you do for a living?
Construction worker
Construction?
Yes
You know, I was scouted by a comedy agent
Right now I'm, uh, uh,
I'm doing extra work in comedy productions
Thank you for helping with that theory
Oh yeah, no trouble
What are you doing today?
Well, I have the day off
I go back to work tomorrow night
Sitting in my room all day would be boring
So you're going to Shibuya?
Yeah, that's right
I spend a lot of time in Shibuya when I have a break
Have there been any consequences?
People greet me a lot
If I go to Ikebukoro-
People will even come up-
and ask to take a photo with me
Oh, hello
We ask him, one of our many friends, who is cuter
The left one, yeah?
However, this photo belongs to the girl on the right
And this is what the girl on the left looks like
The purikura effect completely changed them both
And our final photo
The right one
The blond? Interesting
Left
The decision is 2-1