Everywhere you look, hippopotamus teeth
A small-forehead woman has appeared, but is more than we hoped for
That is really something
That's one in a million
Which feature do people notice?
For real
What would you say your most distinguishing feature is?
I wonder...
I don't want to seem like a lame old person, so I try to stay hip
She seems to think we were asking about her outfit
We're looking for the narrowest forehead in Japan
If that's the case, I'll slide this back a little
It's moving?
It's sliding!
This is it
Well, that's...
Huh?
Oh no
Is it a wig?
It's a wig. This is my real forehead, though.
That's still halfway down though
It was a wig
What is this?
Continuing on
Chiba is getting some on the side
The theory that gave birth to this somewhat different result
That is
If you spilled tea at a Yazawa fan's house, they would never dry it with a Yazawa towel
On this crazy Yazawa fan's way home
We tried our experiment of intentionally spilling tea
And finally we interviewed him
My phone number is also Yazawa
If you take the last 4 numbers
"8-3-0" can be read as "ya-za-wa"
He's fixated on 830
But "8-7-4" is a more accurate number for the 50 year old fan
("8-7-4" can be read to sound like "has no teeth")
So true
Hey!
A Yazawa fan for 38 years
That's just
What are you even saying?
A toothless man with loads of merchandise
That's awful
He doesn't have any friends, does he?
When we asked to take a look
That's so lame
I actually have another place
Oh?
I'll show you the way
It's just for your merchandise?
He's having a laugh
It's just for merch
Wow, amazing
I rent it just for that
Don't you have other expenses?
That's why I rent the room secretly
Is it okay for your wife to know this?
It's fine
So, we went to the room secret even to his wife
Ah, it's like that
This is my other place
Amazing
Could we see inside?
Already you can get a feeling
No way
Right as you enter, even
I made this actually.
You made this?
Yes
He made it
That's cute
But before the Yazawa love can flow
So cute
Hey Chiba-san
Are you messing around?
No that's not it, this is
Well... I just kinda stuck some stuff and...
What was that?
No no no no no
I'm not messing around, nope nope nope
You looked guilty as hell saying that just now
What?
The confusion on his face is obvious
The marks of a woman are even more obvious
You've got Snoopy
Well, you see that's
It's cute. An awfully feminine design don't you think?
It could have been a present
That's bad news
While we're on the topic
Seriously?
That curtain earlier
Oh yeah
Can't possibly be homemade
Wow, this is incredible!
This is seriously cool
This is my pride
So, how much do you pay for this place?
About 70,000 yen
That's not cheap
Is someone splitting the rent?
Why would you ask that?
And things like this were slipped in with the merch
Chiba-san, is this your handwriting?
Ah. Yes this is my writing, of course.
An itinerary for a live show at Budokan is written on the white board
text2
But this handwriting is crazy suspicious
That's weird
For some reason, even Christmas plans are included
You really did right this, then?
What were you feeling when you drew this?
"Let's go to Budokan~♥"
I'll write it now
B
Bu
What a weird stroke order
Bud
Why is he writing like that?
A super weird stroke order
Bud
What is this?
That's amazing
Bud
Budo
It's like he's painting
Budok
What now?
Where's the other half?
Budokn
Ah, that's wrong
No good
Budokn
Chiba is getting some on the side
That totally didn't match the theory
That was exhausting
It really was exhausting, I mean...
Moving on, let's try to answer the question
Wasn't that enough?
Our next theory
He couldn't beat a demon without a pheasant
Oh, I think I know this one
You know this one?
Could Momotaro really rely
Wait really?
Go on
On the dog, monkey, and pheasant to actually help?
Well, you're a little mixed up
Should I try saying that again?
Yes, one more time
Once more- Hamada, you haven't said a damn thing
What's that about?
I don't know a single one of these things
You're always here, though
You can't tame dogs, monkeys, or pheasants with dumplings
First is the dog
Here
Do you want it?
He's taking it
Dogs are omnivorous, so it makes sense
He ate it
He's hungry
He cautiously accepts the dumpling
Where's he going?
But because it's hot, he takes it to the shade to eat
Then, he somehow recruits a monkey
Do you want a dumpling?
The pheasant won't be won over
Momotaro, with just his dog and monkey, set out for the Island of Demons
I've come to defend the peace!
Come on out, demons!
And then
Oh it's Kukki!
What happened?
What's going on?
Kuu-chan?
Scram
Get out of here
Hold on
They just left him there
People with freaking Shonan license plates
Ain't going to impress no one in Yokohama
He couldn't beat a demon without a pheasant
What kind of ending is that?
Actually I was pretty close to the actual theory
You were pretty close
Isn't this guy the worst?
Hamada, at least pay attention. Just focus.
What is going on with you?
Well if you're sitting here thinking of things to say every time, you'll remember
No no no no
I'm always left over there, you know
All I ever do is say "Welcome!!"
Well, Hamada
You sound so proud to be completely neglecting your job
What do you think you get paid for?
Don't just repeat yourself
I wasn't
Please teach me to negotiate a job
Noooooo way
That's a sweet deal
Please pay attention, Hamada, just once
Switching the entrance and exit theory, continued
The youngest and oldest are evenly matched theory
This theory tests what happens when you pit the youngest and oldest athletes against each other in various events
First up is Judo
Representing the oldest
Tadayuki Morimoto, 84 year old ranked 8-dan
Wow
That's impressive
Representing the youngest
Yeah, but
A 5 year old studying Judo in Kumakogen, Toki Sasaki
Isn't he going to get creamed?
As expected, this is the ultimate age difference
Really?
The match is beginning
Ah it's starting
He doesn't look happy
He doesn't like this at all
Does your tummy hurt?
Does his tummy hurt?
He doesn't feel good
What's this? Young Toki is holding his stomach and leaving the ring!
Maybe he needs to pee?
What? Is something wrong?
What happened?
Before the match can start, Toki leaves to go to his family
Why?
He suddenly begins to cry
You're kidding
Fighting an old man he doesn't know is scary
Oh, he's a stranger
It's because he's a stranger
That's so sad, though
At this point, Morimoto approaches the staff
He's going to talk to him
He's describing it so dramatically
Look, he's a 5 year old kid
You shouldn't be making fun of his Judo
He's pissed
You're doing all of this to show on a variety show
I see what you're going for
Oh he's super pissed
But this really goes against the spirit of Judo
Fair enough
He hasn't had any time to learn
But I've been doing this for 64 years
Yes
Making a kid fight me after just 6 months is impossible
Right
He got crazy angry with us
Obviously
So this match ends with forfeit
Oh I see
Are you done?
A few days later, we brought him back with a different opponent
Wait, he's doing it now?
He came back
This time, the opponent is just old enough to compete nationally
Interesting
Way different
This is something
Kanagawa 5th grader Koshiro Sanada
Oh no
This...
He's much better qualified
Morimoto shouldn't have any issues taking him on
He should be fine
Sorry for calling you here a second time
It's fine
Well, he came didn't he?
I didn't think you would, though
He was really mad, though
I won't give up
That's all I'll say about it
Really?
You aren't giving up?
Really
I won't give up
He'll have to retire
Which basically means I'll lose
I see